Woodrow Wilson Collection, 1837-1986 (bulk 1883-1924 ): Preliminary Finding Aid MC168
Public Policy Papers
- Series 10: Papers of Others About Woodrow Wilson, 1837-1986 October 14; 58 boxes; 2 folders
  - Swem, Charles L., 1894-1986 October 14; 24 boxes
    - Woodrow Wilson, 1894-1986 October 14; 20 boxes
      - Writings – speeches, drafts miscellaneous remarks [1894], 1894-1986 October 14; 3 boxes
        - Officers of the Atlantic Fleet, 1917 August 11; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 63)
        - To the soldiers of the National Army, 1917 September 4; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 64)
        - Re trading with the enemy, 1917 September 7; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 65)
        - Establishment of War Trade Board, 1917 October 13; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 66)
        - Re the 65th Congress, 1917 October 6; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 67)
        - Re a Censorship Board October, undated; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 68)
        - Nominations for the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1917 October 13; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 69)
        - Re food for Allies, 1917 October 25; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 70)
        - Re departure from the United States during the war of aliens, 1917 November; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 71)
        - National Saving, 1917 November 16; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 72)
        - To Congress re control of the railroads by the government, 1917 December 26; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 73)
        - Congressional Message, [1918 January 21], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - [1918 January 21], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - To Farmers Conference, 1918 January 31; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - To delegation of Farmers Cooperative and Educational Union, 1918 February 8; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - League of Nations, 1918 March 23; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Labor Day, 1918 September 2; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
        - Opening campaign for Fourth Liberty Loan, 1918 September 27; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
        - To delegation of colored men, 1918 October 1; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - To the Congress, 1918 November 11; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - State Food Administrators, 1918 November 12; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Re United War Work Campaign (seven organizations), 1919-1918; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - Death of Roosevelt, Theodore, [1919 January 7], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - Opening of the Peace Conference, 1919 January 18; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - French Senate, 1919 January 20; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 14)
        - Peace Conference, Paris, 1919 January 25; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 15)
        - League of Nations, 1919 February 14; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 16)
        - Democratic National Committee, 1919 February 14; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 17)
        - Conference of Governors and Mayors, 1919 March 3; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 18)
        - Re League of Nations (Metropolitan Opera House), 1919 March 4; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 19)
        - Amendments to the Agreement regarding the Rhine Frontier, undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 20)
        - Fifth Plenary Session, 1919 April 28; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 21)
        - International Law Society, 1919 May 9; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 22)
        - At the Institute of France, 1919 May 10; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 23)
        - Congressional Message, 1919 May 20; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 24)
        - At dinner in honor of the President-elect of Brazil, 1919 May 26; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 25)
        - Memorial Day, 1919 May 30; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 26)
        - Issued upon leaving France, 1919 June; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 27)
        - At Hotel de Ville, 1919 June 19; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 28)
        - Belgian Chamber of Deputies, 1919 June 19; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 29)
        - At a dinner in his honor given by the King of Belgium, 1919 June 19; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 30)
        - University of Louvain, 1919 June 19; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 31)
        - At luncheon, American Legation, 1919 June 19; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 32)
        - From the President for Polk: re Kolchak, 1914 June 24; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 33)
        - Memorandum with regard to the Adriatic Question, 1919 June 25; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 34)
        - At President Poincare's House, 1919 June 26; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - Re peace treaty, [1919 June 28], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 36)
        - Italy vis-à-vis the Allies, 1919 June 28; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 37)
        - On board the George Washington, 1919 July 4; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 38)
        - At Carnegie Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 39)
        - To the Senate on the peace treaty with Germany, [1919 July 10], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 40)
        - On reviewing a detachment of the Czechoslovak Army, Works, Miscellaneous Remarks, 1919 July 18; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 41)
        - Armistice – World War I, [1919-1920], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 42)
        - Congressional Message, [1919-1920], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 43)
        - Transcript of Conference with Woodrow Wilson and Senate Committee (including senators Lodge, Borah, Knox, Hitchcock, et al), [1919-1920], dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 44)
        - Re United States mandate over Armenia (Democratic platform 1920), [1920], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 45)
        - Message to Congress, 1920 May 24; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 46)
        - To the House of Representatives, 1920 May 27; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 47)
        - To Health Crusaders, 1920 June 14; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 48)
        - Re League of Nations, 1920 October 4; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 49)
        - Re League of Nations, 1920 October 27; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 50)
        - Annual Congressional Message, 1920 December 7; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 51)
        - Notes, drafts, outlines etc, 1912-1920; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 52)
        - Works, undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 53)
        - 7 Notes to Swem, Charles L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 54)
        - Note to Swem, Charles L., [1915], undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 54)
        - Note to Swem, Charles L, 1917; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 54)
        - Fragments Works, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 55)
        - Miscellaneous Notes Works, undated; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, 1907 March-1921 March 7; 1 box
        - Adamson, William, TL (carbon), 1917 April 14; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - Baer, J. M., TL (fragment), [1918 February 18], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Baker, Newton D., TL (signature cut off), 1917 June 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Barrett, John, telegram (copy), 1915 December 27; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Baruch, Bernard L., TL (draft) fragment, [1918 March 5], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Bennet, William S., TL (signature cut off), 1916 March 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Bennet, William S., TL (carbon), 1916 March 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - TLS by Bennet to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 March 15; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - The Editor – The Boston Evening Record TL (carbon) –, 1920 November 19; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Bridgeman, W. R., telegram to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 October 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Bridgeman, W. R., telegram by Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 November 1; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - "Bryan" [William Jennings] telegram (in code) to Wilson, Woodrow, 1913 September 1; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Burelson, Albert S., 2 TLS (carbons), 1920 July 14; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Burelson, Albert S., TL (copy), 1920 July 14; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - TLS by Burelson, Albert S., to Wilson, Woodrow, 1918 June 28; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Burelson, Albert S., TL (signature cut off), 1916 April 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Cannon, James Jr., draft of a letter in shorthand [1917 June 17], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Carlin, Charles C., TL (copy), TL (carbon), 1916 July 12; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Chamberlain, George E., TL (copy), 1918 January 11; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Chandler, William E., TL (copy), 1914 December 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Clark, Frank, TL (draft), 1917 November 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - Close, Gilbert F., ANS (initialed), 1919 May 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - Colby, Bainbridge, AL (draft), [1920 November 6], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - Crane, Charles R., ANS, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 18)
        - Culberson, Charles A., TL (carbon), 1917 April 14; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 19)
        - "Cummings", 5 telegrams, by Cummings to Wilson, Woodrow, 1920 June; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 20)
        - Daniels, Josephus, TL (copy), 1915 July 31; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Daniels, Josephus, TL (fragment), 1915 July 21; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Davidson, Henry P., ALS, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - Fergusson, H. B., TL (copy), 1914 May 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 23)
        - George, David Lloyd, TL (draft) (fragment), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 24)
        - Goode, M. O., TLS, 1912 August 22; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 25)
        - Hale, Matthew, TLS, 1917 October 2; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 26)
        - Hamaker, G. E. [telegram], 1920 May 9; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 27)
        - Hariman, Karl Edwin, TL (carbon), 1915 February 12; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 28)
        - Herriott, David, ALS to Wilson, Woodrow including photostats of 6 original letters sent to Lincoln, Abraham, 1913 February 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 29)
        - Hines, Walker D., TL (draft), 1920 May 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 30)
        - Hitchcock, Gilbert M., TL (draft), 2 TLS (copies), 1920 March; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 31)
        - House, E. M., TL (copy), 1919 July 1; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 32)
        - Houston, D. F., TLS by Houston to Wilson, Woodrow, 1920 December 2; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 33)
        - Houston, D. [cable draft], 1919 March 31; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 33)
        - Hurlbut, C. H., (Mrs.), TL (carbon), 1914 November 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 34)
        - "Gentlemen" including Jewell, B. B., Shea, Timothy, Hunion, E. J. et al., undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 35)
        - Horne, Joseph (Co.), TLS by Shea, J. B., for Hurne, Joseph, to Wilson, Woodrow, 1907 March 26; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 36)
        - Kent, William, TLS by Kent to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 July 8; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 37)
        - Kitchen, Claude, TL (signature cut out), enclosed TL (copy) to Byrnes, James F, 1917 May 16; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 38)
        - Lansing, Robert, telegram (draft), 1916 February 2; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 38a)
        - Lansing, Robert, TL (copy) by Lansing to Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 August 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 38a)
        - Lansing, Robert, TLS (initialed), 1917 May 11; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 38a)
        - M. Larnavde, TL (draft) with AN initialed, 1920 October 8; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 39)
        - Leffingwell, R. C., TL (draft), [1920 April 15], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 40)
        - Lippmann, Walter, telegram (draft), 1916 October 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 41)
        - TL (carbon), 1917 November 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 42)
        - [McAdoo, William Gibbs], draft of cable, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 43)
        - [McAdoo, William Gibbs], TL (draft), 1914 November 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 43)
        - McAllister, Elizabeth Wilton to Woodrow Wilson, TL (copy), [1920] September 27, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 44)
        - McFadden, Neila, TL (draft), 1920 December 15; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 45)
        - McFadden, Neila, TL (carbon), 1920 December 16; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 45)
        - McRae, Milton A., TLS, 1916 October 9; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 46)
        - Merrill, Elmer Truesdale, TL (copy) to Wilson, Woodrow, 1915 January 15; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 47)
        - Newlands, Francis G., TLS to Wilson, Woodrow, including bill to create an Interstate Trade Commission, 1913 September 29; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 48)
        - O'Leary, J. A., telegram-draft, [1916 September 29], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 49)
        - Operators and Miners of the Anthracite Wage Scale Committee, TL (copy), 1920 May 21; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 50)
        - Orlando, [Vittorio E.], TLS (draft), TL (draft), 1919 January 10; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 51)
        - Overman, Lee S., TLS by Overman to Wilson, Woodrow, 1917 June 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 52)
        - Page, Thomas Nelson, TL 9carbon) including a list of personnel (2 copies), 1918 December 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 53)
        - Palmer, A. Mitchell, TL (copy), 1920 July 31; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 54)
        - Parker, Edwin B., TLS, 1919 March 22; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 55)
        - Pindell, Henry M., TL (signature cut off), [1914 February 2], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 56)
        - Mr. Polk, Acting Secretary of State, Cipher Cable-Green Code, 1919 March 10; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 57)
        - Redfield, William C., TLS by Redfield to Woodrow Wilson, 1917 June 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 58)
        - Redfield, William C., TLS by Redfield to Wilson, Woodrow, TL (copy), 1917 June 18; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 58)
        - "Regrets" to 7 mayors of cities in England and Scotland, TLS (copies), Undated, 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 59)
        - Roper, D. C., TL (draft), 1920 March 5; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 60)
        - Sisson, Edgar G., TLS, 1917 October 24; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 61)
        - de Spoelberch, Pussy and de Spoelberch, E., TL (copy) by the Spoelberches to Wilson, Woodrow, 1915 February 18; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 62)
        - de Spoelberch, Pussy and de Spoelberch, E., TL (copy), 1915 March 20; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 62)
        - Swem, Charles L., TLS by Swem to Wilson, Woodrow, 1919 March 13; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 63)
        - Swem, Charles L. – Official business for Woodrow Wilson American Commission to Negotiate Peace, 1919 May 29; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 64)
        - Bolling, John Randolph – TLS, 1921 March 7; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 64)
        - Bones, Helen Woodrow, 1 ALS, 1916 January 28; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 64)
        - Bones, Helen Woodrow, 2 ALsS, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 64)
        - Thompson, William B., TL (fragment), 1917 October 24; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 65)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., TNS (initialed), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 66)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., TL (carbon), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 66)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., telegram (copy), 1919 June 28; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 66)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., (corr. by Tumulty to Wilson, Woodrow), TLS, 1917 September 17; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 67)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., (corr. by Tumulty to Wilson, Woodrow), TLS, 1917 November 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 67)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., (corr. by Tumulty to Wilson, Woodrow), telegram (draft), 1919 April 18; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 67)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., (corr. by Tumulty to Wilson, Woodrow), telegram, 1919 June 27; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 67)
        - Tumulty, Joseph P., 5 cablegrams, 1919 March-July; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 68)
        - United States Anthracite Coal Commission, TL (copy), 1920 August 30; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 69)
        - Thompson, W. O., Connell, W. L., Ferry, Neal J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 69)
        - Underwood, Oscar W., TL (draft), [1914 October 17], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 70)
        - Wall and Ochs ANS, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 71)
        - Wescott, John W., TL (copy), 1916 May 2; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 72)
        - White, Beaver, TL (draft), undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 73)
        - William II, German Emperor, TL (copy and translation), 1920; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 74)
        - Williams, E., ALS by Williams to Wilson, Woodrow, 1917 November 3; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 75)
        - TN to Tumulty, Joseph P. by Wilson, Woodrow, 1917 November 21; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 75)
        - Wilson, Ida Gordon, ALS by Wilson to Wilson, Woodrow, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 76)
        - Wilson, Margaret, telegram (draft), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 77)
        - [Wilson, William B.], outline of [letter], [1917-1918], undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 78)
        - Woods, Lawrence C., 4 TLsS by Woods to Wilson, Woodrow, 1907 March; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 79)
        - Unidentified, undated; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 80)
      - Shorthand Notebooks, 1-74, undated; 3 boxes
        - Lists of notebooks and transcriptions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Swem notebooks in the Library of Congress, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Swem notebooks, 1-26, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - Swem notebooks, 27-52, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Swem notebooks, 53-74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - Measday Book, undated; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Xeroxes of Shorthand Notebooks, 1-4, 1912 August 29-1913 January 13; 2 boxes
        - Shorthand notebooks, Xerox copies books 1-3, –, 1912 August 29; 1912 October 22; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
        - Shorthand notebooks, Xerox copies, book 4, –, 1912 October 29; 1912 October 20; 1913 January 13; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Transcripts of Speeches and Press Conferences, 1912-1914; 1 box
        - Chronological Index, undated; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
        - Notes, 1912; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
        - 1912 August, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
        - 1912 September, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
        - 1912 October, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
        - 1912 November-December, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 6)
        - Unidentified, 1912; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Fragments, 1912; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - 1913 March, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 9)
        - 1913 April, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 10)
        - 1913 May, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 11)
        - 1913 June, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 12)
        - 1913 July, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 13)
        - 1913, 1913 August-October; 1913 November; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 14)
        - 1914 January, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 15)
        - 1914 February, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 16)
        - 1914 March, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 17)
        - 1914 April, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 18)
        - 1914 May – 1914 June, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 19)
        - 1914 August, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 20)
        - 1914 September, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 21)
        - 1914 October, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 22)
        - 1914 December, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - Speeches, etc. 1915-1920 Typed Transcripts, 1 box
        - 1915 January, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - 1915 February, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
        - 1915 March, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
        - 1915 April – 1915 May, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
        - 1915 June-December, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
        - 1916, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
        - 1917-1918, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
        - 1919, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
        - 1920, 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
        - undated, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
        - Fragments, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
        - Duplicates, undated; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Transcripts of Correspondence, 1912 November-1921 October; 2 boxes
        - Chronological Index to the typed transcripts, undated; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - (Bermuda), –, 1912 November; 1912 December; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
        - 1913 March – 1913 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
        - 1914 January – 1914 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
        - 1915 January – 1915 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - 1916 January – 1916 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
        - 1917 January – 1917 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
        - 1918 January – 1918 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
        - 1918 July – 1918 December, 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
        - 1919 January – 1919 May, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
        - 1919 June – 1919 July, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
        - 1920 February – 1920 December, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
        - 1921 January – 1921 October, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
        - Addenda, 1915–1921, undated; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 5)
        - undated, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Xeroxes of Transcripts of Correspondence, 1918-1921 October; 3 boxes
        - 1912–1917, undated; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
        - 1918 January – 1918 June, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
        - 1918 July – 1918 December, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
        - 1919 January – 1919 May, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
        - 1919 June – 1919 July, 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
        - 1920 February – 1920 December, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
        - 1921 January – 1921 October, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
        - undated, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Documents, 1916 February-1925; 1 box
        - 2 petitions for Thorton, John Randolph by members of Senate and House of Representatives, 1916 February 1; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
        - Transfer of property by Wilson, Woodrow's mother's forebears in the County of Suffolk, England (Woodrow, Jessie), 1925; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Photographs, 1919; 1 box
        - Wilson, Ellen Axson, by Yates, Frederic, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
        - Wilson, Woodrow (and others), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
        - Italy, 1919; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Memorabilia, undated; 1 box
        - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Material, 1915 February 15-1919; 1 box
        - Codes – broad, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - Copies of Works appearing in print, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
        - General, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
        - Itineraries, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
        - Mexico, Preliminary report by West, Duval, 1915 February 15; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
        - Papers sent to the President, 1919; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
        - Peace Conference, 1918–1919, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
        - Peace Conference (printed matter), 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
        - Political matters, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
        - Presidential Engagements, 1919; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
        - United States Government, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
        - Shorthand Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Printed Matter, 1904-1920; 2 boxes
        - Addresses, 1904-1912; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 1)
        - Addresses, 1913; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 2)
        - Addresses, 1914; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 3)
        - Addresses, 1915; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 4)
        - Addresses, 1916; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 5)
        - Addresses, 1917; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 6)
        - Addresses, 1918; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 7)
        - Addresses, 1920; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 8)
        - Addresses, 1919; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 9)